本作品之片源来自互联网，仅供学习、交流之用。请自觉于下载后24小时内删除。任何组织和个人不得用于任何商业用途，否则一切后果请自行承担！如果喜欢本片，请购买正版！
真不错
Nice.
小心  银发老帅哥出没
别忘记带上杀虫喷剂
And don't forget bug spray.
谁想搭车  就喷谁一脸
It's perfect for spraying in the face of hitchhikers.
哇  房车  露营装备
Whoa! An RV, camping gear.
你是又要畏罪潜逃了吗
Are you running from the law again?
哥们儿  这可是俄勒冈自驾游超级大冒险
Dude, it's the ultimate Oregon road trip adventure.
不如说是复仇之旅
More like revenge trip.
每年  坑游客钱的竞争对手都会对神秘小屋搞恶作剧
Every year, my tourist trap competitors prank the Mystery Shack.
去年这帮流氓把苏斯用胶带粘在了天花板上
Last year, those hooligans duct taped Soos to the ceiling.
那七十八个小时挺好玩的
That was a fun 78 hours.
以后不会这样了
Well, no more.
今年  我们顺着
This year, we're visiting
红杉高速公路游遍所有的专坑游客的景点
every tourist trap along the Redwood Highway,
我要把他们所有人都耍一遍
and I'm gonna prank back every single one.
是时候让公路姐妹团大显身手了
Time to let the Road Dawgs bark.
公路姐妹团  就是我们
That is us. We are the Road Dawgs.
谢谢你让我带格兰达和糖糖一起
Thanks for letting me bring Candy and Grenda along
参加自驾游  斯坦叔公
for our road trip, Grunkle Stan.
人越多  越热闹
The more, the merrier.
把这些含糊其辞的免责协议签了就好
Just sign these non-disclosure agreements.
你们爸妈没人是律师吧
None of your parents are lawyers, right?
你觉得咋样  哥们儿  一起来吧
What do you say, dude? You comin'?
我已经帮你把你的东西都打包好了
I already went to the trouble of packing all your stuff.
还带上了你藏在床底下的秘密小盒子
Even the stuff you kept in that secret box under the bed.
不许碰！
哎呀  怎么
Whoa! What the...
这是什么
What's that?
呃  什么都不是
Uh, nothing.
温蒂的  以前的东西
Just Wendy stuff, from old times.
弟弟  我还以为你终于能放下她了
Bro, I thought you were finally past all this.
我知道  我知道
I know, I know.
我知道她对我不感兴趣  我们结束了
I know she's not interested,and I know it's over,
但是对一个人的感情怎么可能说断就断呢
but how do you just turn off the way you feel about someone?
迪普  给你两个词  移情别恋
Two words, Dipper. Move on.
对啊  哥们儿  要是想遇见新朋友
Yeah, dude, and a road trip's the perfect place
自驾游再合适不过了
to meet new people.
重新发现自我  踏上阳关大道
■
本字幕由★迪幻字幕组★为您奉献
欢迎登录www.Deefun.com
■
时间轴： Enpistu
翻译： 战忽局副局座  溪傲季  moonywen
■
校订  后期： Enpistu  WaitinZ
怪诞小镇  第二季第十六集
Gravity Falls  S02E16  Roadside Attraction
哎呀  房车真是爽
Man, RV's are amazing.
真不敢相信在飞驰的车里还能围坐桌旁
I can't believe we're sitting at a table in a moving vehicle.
哟  旅行信息小册子
Ooh! Informational travel pamphlets.
我要好好读一遍  汲取旅游的知识
I want to read them all and gain their travel knowledge.
孩子  这堆破册子里压根没啥知识
Kid, those useless pamphlets have never helped a single person.
有我这个满脸皱纹的老导游在就够了
The only wrinkly old travel guide you'll need is me.
赶紧的
Now look alive.
第一个景点马上就到
We're coming up on an attraction
全俄勒冈州最黑心的老板就在这里
run by the most black-hearted proprietor in all of Oregon.
甜心奶奶的毛线球  世界最大
别让她的面容给忽悠了
Don't let the face fool you.
这老太婆把我的车
This woman lit my car on fire
点着火了两次
on two non-consecutive occasions.
姑娘们  我要进去了
I'm going in, girls.
好  听苏斯的话
Okay, like Soos said,
认识新朋友
meet new people.
呃  经常来这儿吗
So, uh, come here often?
不  我是来旅游的
No. I'm a tourist.
哈哈  你真好玩  挺可爱的
Ha ha, you're funny... and cute.
不  不可爱
I mean, not cute.
我是说  你并不是不可爱
I mean, you're not not cute.
呼  让我重来一遍
Whew, let me start over.
我的名字叫多普
My name is Dopper.
迪普  快上
Dipper, hop to.
毛线球可不会自己拆自己
This ball of yarn ain't gonna prank itself.
小鬼  有啥心事啊
Something on your mind, kiddo?
还想着刚才那位臭脸小妞呢
Thinkin' about Miss Cold Shoulder over there, huh?
真是尴尬死了
Ah, so embarrassed.
听着  暑假前阵子  我把和温蒂在一起的机会搞砸了
Look, earlier this summer, I ruined my chances with Wendy.
呵呵  机会
Yeah. Chances.
我也想移情别恋  但我压根不会跟女孩说话
And I wanna move on, but I'm terrible at talking to girls.
一旦要开口对她们讲话
The moment I open my mouth around them,
我就好像散了架  就像
I unravel like... like...
我想不出来怎么打比喻  你领会就好
well, I can't think of a perfect metaphor, but you get the gist.
照这样下去  我大概会像
At this rate, I'm gonna grow up
托比・迪特敏德一样悲哀地孤独终老了
to be a sad loner like Toby Determined.
千万别这么糟践自己
Whoa, never say that about yourself.
算你好运  我可是个泡妞专家
Lucky for you, I'm an expert on women.
听我说  孩子
Listen to me, kid.
和女孩子打交道  首先要保持自信
When it comes to girls, always be confident,
要有幽默感  但别太过
and be funny, but not too funny.
要有点烦人  但是要让人意乱情迷
And be kind of annoying, but in a loveable way.
我不知道  斯坦叔公  听起来有点混蛋啊
I don't know, Grunkle Stan. This sounds kinda jerky.
“混蛋”这个词是混蛋不起来的人
Hey, "Jerky" Is just a term non-jerks use
用来侮辱无辜混蛋的
to bad-mouth innocent jerks.
自信  幽默  再帮我想个意思差不多的词
Confidence, comedy, some third word starting with a "C."
这三个要点就是斯坦・派恩斯的约会秘诀
The three C's of the Stan Pines Dating Technique.
到了下个景点
At the next tourist trap,
见到一个女孩子就试试我的办法
try out my advice on the first girl you see.
好  斯坦叔公  谢谢
Cool. Grunkle Stan, thanks.
我满脑子可都是好主意
Hey, I'm full of good ideas.
说到好主意嘛
Speakin' of which,
大家快上车啊
everyone, now!
混蛋  你个无耻贱人
Why, you gol-darned son of a no-good!
全世界最大的毛衣针
斯坦・派恩斯  看我不逮住你
I'll get you, Stan Pines!
这不是幻觉！距离倒立小屋只有三十英里！
啊  倒立小屋
Ah, Upside-down Town.
全州闻名的反胃之都
The nausea capital of the state.
不管干什么  都千万别去上厕所
Whatever you do, don't use the bathrooms.
公路姐妹团
Road Dawgs!
-哇  -感觉怪怪的
- Whoa! - So weird.
听好了  孩子  记住要领
All right, kid, this is it.
保持自信
Be confident.
你好  我是迪普
Hi. I'm Dipper.
这地方真奇怪  对吧
Crazy place, right?
你好  我叫艾玛・苏
Oh, hi. I'm Emma Sue.
如果你假装我们脑袋朝上的话
If you pretend we're right-side up,
看起来就像大家头发都竖起来了
it looks like everyone's hair is standing on end.
哈  对啊  真是奇怪
Huh, yeah. Weird, right?
你假装尖叫试试
Pretend you're screaming.
好  不过你得帮我拍照啊
Okay. You gotta take a picture of me, though.
看看怎  哎呀
Let's see... whoa!
哈哈  吓着了吧
Ho ho, just kidding.
你真够坏的
You are the worst.
可不是嘛
You bet I am.
我可坏了  艾玛
I'm bad, Emma.
有点像个混蛋
Kind of a jerk.
艾玛  快跟上  咱们得在你妈
Emma, come on. We have to get to Canada
生孩子前赶到加拿大
before your mother gives birth.
说来话长了
It's a long story.
也许你哪天有时间能跟我说说
Maybe you could tell me sometime.
这是我的邮箱地址
Here's my email address.
给我发邮件  我会全都告诉你的
Write me and I'll tell you all about it.
有女生给我邮箱地址了
A girl gave me her email,
而且并不是出于怜悯
and it wasn't out of pity.
哈哈  太棒了
Ha ha, yes!
我很好
Ugh! I'm okay.
比很好还要好
I'm better than okay.
好啊梅宝  格兰达你咋样啊
Mabel, hi. There's my Grenda.
糖糖  挺漂亮  挺漂亮
Candy, looking great, looking great.
是不是换了副眼镜啊  亮闪闪的
Is that a new pair of glasses? Very shiny.
是不是我脑袋积血了
Maybe it's the blood pooling in my head,
迪普似乎不一样了
but Dipper seems different.
对  变得更好了
Yes, good different.
苏斯  快行动
Now, Soos.
现在看你还怎么倒立
Not too upside-down now.
真是个无比正常的漂亮房子啊
What a lovely normal home.
斯坦・派恩斯
Stan Pines!
真不敢相信奏效了
I can't believe it worked.
现在我该怎么做  给她发邮件吗
What do I do now? Do I email her?
不  不  你要练习
No, no, you practice.
跟越多的女孩子谈话  你的技巧就会越娴熟
The more girls you talk to, the better you get at it.
斯坦叔公  这些经验真是无价之宝啊
Grunkle Stan, these tips are priceless.
这只能算我丰富经验的冰山一角
And that's just the tip of the advice-berg.
原木乐园
玉米迷宫
玉米象鼻虫
-人都齐了吧  -应该齐了
- Everyone on board? - Probably.
伙计们  人呢
Guys? Hello?
有人吗
Anyone?
他们会回来找我的
They'll come back for me.
然后我跟门卫说
So then I said to the bouncer,
“丑八怪  你的身份证又在哪儿”
"Where's your ID, ugly?"
我这条伤疤就是这么来的
That's where I got this scar.
斯坦叔公  我必须得说
Grunkle Stan, I gotta say,
今天算是我人生最美好的一天
this was one of the best days ever.
快看
Look!
这就是斯坦・派恩斯的秘诀  小鬼
That's the Stan Pines method, kid.
百试百灵
Works every time.
可是  我有些担心
I'm just a little worried, though.
我是指  一次和这么多女孩调情  不合适吧
I mean, is it bad to flirt with this many girls at once?
我只是想放下温蒂而已
I'm just trying to get over Wendy.
我不想伤任何人的心
I don't wanna hurt anyone's feelings.
拜托  这就是自驾游时调情最大的好处
Please. That's the best part of flirting on a road trip.
你再也不会见到这些女孩子们
You're not gonna see any of these gals again.
敬  移情别恋
To moving on.
好啦  是时候玩
Okay, it's time for...
真心话和大冒险和玩不起啦
Truth or dare or don't!
我选择玩不起
I choose don't.
你总是选择玩不起
You always choose don't.
好吧  那就  真心话
Fine. Uh... truth.
你有喜欢的人吗
Do you like someone?
喔  有人脸红啦
Uh-oh. Someone's blushing.
好吧  也许有一点点
Okay, maybe just a little.
我自己也不清楚  这感觉才刚开始
I don't know for sure. It just started.
快说  快说
Tell us, tell us!
好吧  他名字以“迪”开头
Okay. It begins with a "D,"
以“普”结尾
and ends with an "ipper."
-不会吧  -是的
- No. - Yes.
准备好了吗  格兰达  三  二  一
Ready, Grenda? Three, two, one.
天  郊狼的叫声比我记忆中的难听多了
Man, coyotes sound a lot worse than I remember.
糖糖  糖糖  我的人生梦想全都要实现了
Candy, Candy, all my life dreams are coming true right now.
我弟弟  我最好的朋友
My brother, my best friend.
我无法呼吸
I can't breathe!
我太激动了  喘不过气
I'm so excited, I can't breathe!
以前  我从没真正地注意过他
I never really noticed him before,
不过他最近似乎变得深沉了
but he seems deeper lately,
流汗少了些  也更迷人了
less sweaty and more charming.
但是我该怎么接近他呢
But how do I approach him?
那种事用不着担心  小糖糖
Don't even worry about that, Can-Can.
梅宝有个计划
Mabel's got a plan.
好啦  小营员们  我们迎来了又一个
All right, campers, we got another day
违法犯罪让别人心碎的日子
of breakin' laws and breakin' hearts.
目前为止的一切  和我们下一个目标相比
Everything up until now has been a walk in the park
都不过是公园遛弯级别的小儿科
compared to our next attraction.
是在世界上最大的公园遛弯吗
Is it a walk in the world's biggest park?
差不多  我们到了  孩子们
Sort of. There she is, kids.
神秘山
Mystery Mountain.
这里是神秘小屋的五倍大
Five times the size of the Mystery Shack,
更可怕的是  她有真正的景点
and what's worse, she has real attractions.
我读到过这个地方
Oh, I have read about this place.
这里有登山缆车  木乃伊博物馆
It has sky tram, and a mummy museum,
还能看到半人半蜘蛛的生物
and sightings of half-human, half-spider creatures.
他们就连瞎编的传说都比我们的好
Even their made-up legends are better than ours.
今天  这座山将沦陷
Today, the mountain falls.
请问  我坐在后座晕车
Question. The backseat makes me carsick.
今天我能坐前面吗
Can I sit up front today?
我也想问  我体型一个顶俩
Also a question. I'm the size of two people.
我能一个人占整个座位吗
Can I have a whole seat to myself?
不知道  行呗
I don't know. Sure.
换位置
Ooh, change-up!
等等  也就是说  这儿只有我和
Wait, that means it'll be just me and...
糖糖・秋  六年级
Candy Chu. Sixth grade.
噢  嘿
Oh! Hey.
你坐得好近
You're sitting close.
迪普  我很好奇
So Dipper, I was wondering,
你今天想不想和我一起
would you maybe want to walk around
去神秘山转一转呢
the Mystery Mountain with me today?
当然  我是说
Sure. I mean...
这不就是我们的计划吗
wasn't that already the plan?
我是指  就我们两个
I mean, just us.
我和你  糖糖和迪普
You and me. Candy and Dipper.
好啦  公路姐妹团  谁去把那头蓝色的公牛翻倒
All right, Road Dawgs, I got five bucks
我就奖励谁五块钱
for whoever can tip the big blue ox.
快去吧
Go, go, go.
我们在那儿见
I will see you in there.
孩子  你怎么一脸无精打采的样子
Hey, what's with the mopey mug, kid?
斯坦叔公  你得帮我
Stan, you gotta help me.
你教我的每件事  效果都好过了头
Everything you taught me worked too well.
我觉得糖糖刚才想和我约会呢
I think Candy just asked me out on a date.
嘿  看看你这个小冠军
Hey, look at this little champion.
什么  不  我是说
What? No. I mean...
糖糖人挺好的  甜美可爱  聪明伶俐
Candy's great, she's sweet, and she's smart,
但是我对她从来都没有那种想法
but I never thought of her like that.
这事进展得太快了
This is all moving way too fast.
好吧  我应该对她实话实说
Okay, I just need to be honest with her,
告诉她这件事我还没有准备好
and tell her I'm not ready for all this.
你还不明白发生了什么吗
Don't you see what's happening here?
你对温蒂愚蠢的迷恋  阻碍了你的大好未来
That's your dumb obsession with Wendy gettin' in the way of your future.
如果你想要移情别恋
If you wanna move on,
不管是谁来找你  你都要答应
you gotta say yes to whatever comes your way.
说起来
Speaking of which...
但是我不想骗她
But I don't wanna lead her on.
仔细瞧  好好学
Uh-uh-uh, watch and learn.
我好像把自己的电话号码给弄丢了
Whoa, I seem to have lost my number.
能借你的用用吗
Can I borrow yours?
你这个小傻瓜
You are a riot.
什么风把你吹到这里来了
What brings you here?
我们这一片儿通常都看不到你这样的帅哥
We don't normally get men this handsome round these parts.
那个  达琳
Well, Darlene,
我在这里干啥  是你我之间的小秘密
between you and me, what I'm doin' here is a little secret.
你看上去就是一个有秘密的男人
Oh, you seem like a man with secrets.
我要下班了  你懂的
You know, I'm going on a break.
想不想坐缆车上寡妇之巅看看
You wanna take the sky tram up to Widow's Peak?
听不听建议随便你
Take my advice or don't,
不过很明显  我这儿进展不错
but clearly, I know what I'm doing.
好极了
Oh, fancy.
不敢相信  这事真的发生了
Oh, I can't believe this is happening.
一个真正的约会
A real date.
我想知道他们会给孩子取什么名字
I wonder what they'll name the baby.
如果我有个孩子  我会叫他
If I had a baby, I would name it
格兰达第二部  续集
Grenda 2: The Sequel.
你一定会是个好母亲
You would make such a good mother.
这个地方如此迷人
This place is so enchanting.
虽然“每日最新木乃伊”这个说法
Sort of confused by the phrase
让人摸不着头脑
"new mummies daily" though.
我是说  这根本解释不通啊
I mean, how does that even work?
这座山满是未解之谜
This mountain's full of mysteries.
就像为什么我的头会靠上你的肩
Like why is my head falling on your shoulder?
没错  这就是我想要的
Uh, yep, this is what I want.
这不过是计划的一部分
This is all part of the plan and stuff.
迪普  喂
Oh, Dipper, hey.
玉米迷宫的女孩
Corn maze girl.
我想知道你什么时候会给我打电话
I was wondering when you'd call.
迪普  她是谁
Dipper, who is this?
谁也不是  我是说  她是某个人  但是
Nobody. I mean, uh... somebody, but...
迪普
Dipper!
从侧面差点没认出来你
I didn't recognize you right-side up.
你绝对想不到我妈妈是在哪里生的孩子
You'll never guess where my mom gave birth.
喂  这些女孩子是什么人
Hey, who are these girls?
迪普  你怎么没给我打电话
Dipper, why haven't you called?
我们的浪漫原木之旅对你来说无足轻重吗
Did our romantic log ride mean nothing to you?
真不敢相信
I can't believe it.
你答应和我约会的同时
You agreed to go on a date with me,
也和所有这些女生约会吗
and you are seeing all these other girls?
回答我们  你最喜欢我们中的谁
Well, answer us. Which one of us do you like?
我  我全都喜欢
I... I like all of you.
我是说  我一个也不喜欢
I mean, I don't like any of you.
我是说
I mean...
我只是在努力学习如何和女孩子搭讪
I was trying to learn how to talk to girls.
-难以置信  -真讨厌
- Unbelievable. - So gross.
真是个混蛋
What a jerk.
迪普・派恩斯  我以为你是个好男孩
Dipper Pines, I thought you were a nice guy,
但是  恐怕你只关心自己吧
but I guess you only care about yourself.
糖糖  等等
Uh, Candy, wait.
我把一切都搞砸了
I messed everything up.
我得去找斯坦叔公  他知道该怎么办
I gotta find Stan. He'll know what to do.
你确定要往森林里走这么深吗
Oh, are you sure you wanna go this deep into the forest?
这里好可怕
It's so scary.
别担心  亲爱的
Don't worry, toots.
蜘蛛人之类的东西只是都市传说
That spider people stuff is just an urban legend.
不敢相信竟然有人会买账
I can't believe people fall for it.
你太勇敢啦
You're so brave.
那当然了  我可是人中尤物
What can I say? I'm a real catch.
没错
Yes.
今天你就是我的猎物了
The catch of the day.
呃  你的隐形眼镜好像掉了
Uh, I think your contacts fell out.
请问你有没有在附近看到一个老头
Uh, have you seen an old guy around here?
大耳朵  橘色鼻子  是个万事通
Big ears, orange nose, a real know-it-all.
听好啦  浣熊防火员提醒您
Uh-uh-uh. Flame retardant raccoon says,
不要和森林火灾做朋友噢
don't hug forest fires.
斯坦  你在哪里  我需要你的建议
Stan, where are you? I need your advice.
斯坦叔公
Grunkle Stan?
嘿  小伙子
Hey, buddy boy.
还记得我给你说过的搭讪技巧吗
Remember how we were talkin' about my technique?
有时候也会产生一些意想不到的后果啦
Well, sometimes it leads to unexpected consequences.
是啊  说得对极了  你在哪儿
Yeah, you can say that again. Where are you?
好消息是  我解决了俄勒冈州
The good news is, I've solved the mystery
木乃伊的来源疑团
of where Oregon's mummies come from.
坏消息是
The bad news is,
我就要成为他们的一员了
I'm about to become one.
原来达琳就是那传说中的蜘蛛人
Turns out Darlene is one of those spider people.
不过除此之外  我们的约会还挺顺利的
But beyond that, the date's been okay.
等等  等等  达琳是蜘蛛人
Wait, wait, wait. Darlene's a spider person?
这怎么可能呢
How is that possible?
我不知道
I don't know.
前一分钟  我们还在愉快地约会
One minute, we're having a perfect date,
后一分钟  她就长出了很多蜘蛛腿
and the next minute, she's growing extra legs
用网把我包了起来  女人啊  对吧
and encasing me in webbing. Women, right?
你竟然分辨不出她是一只蜘蛛
You couldn't tell she was a spider?!
我被甜言蜜语蒙蔽了
I was blinded by flattery.
还有她喷在我脸上的酸汁
Also this acid she spit in my face.
我在寡妇之巅的山顶
I'm up the mountain at Widow's Peak.
好  我会找到你的  呆在原地别动
All right, I'm gonna find you. Stay put!
知道啦
You got it.
怎么  想逃跑吗
Uh-uh. Trying to escape?
你骗了我
You tricked me.
我百分之八十确信你一点也不爱我
I'm 80% certain you don't really love me at all.
哈  男人真是什么都信
Ha! Men will fall for anything.
“你真有趣  故事很棒
"You're so funny. Great story.
我喜欢肩上长毛的男人”
I love a man with shoulder hair."
你  你不是真心喜欢我的肩上的毛吗
You... you didn't mean it about my shoulder hair?
告诉我  斯坦  在我变身之前
Tell me, Stan, before I transformed,
你以为咱俩谁主导着局面
who'd you think was in charge?
就凭你那做作的开场白和虚假的自信心吗
You, with your cheesy lines and fake confidence?
我才是这里的搭讪大师
I'm the master pick-up artist here.
抱歉了  亲爱的
Sorry, toots.
这回  你的身体要派上用场了
This time, you're getting used for your body,
对我这种奇怪的生物来说  就是食物哦
which, to my weird species, is food.
允许我再变个更可怕点的形象
Allow me to slip into something more horrifying.
我得想想该拿什么饮料来配
I wonder what beverage pairs well
一个七十多岁的老头子
with a vintage 70-something-year-old man.
马上回来
Be right back.
快来啊  迪普  你在哪里
Come on, Dipper, where are you?
我觉得自己是个傻瓜
I feel like such a fool.
我本该知道冰封自己的心才能远离伤害
I should have known to guard my heart in a cage of ice.
好了  好了  用我平静的声音来安慰你吧
There, there. Let my calming voice soothe you.
感觉好多了
It is helping.
姑娘们  你们在这儿
Girls, there you are.
-负心汉  -是你  你想要什么
- Betrayer! - Oh, you. What do you want?
-我需要你们的帮助  -帮什么  又是什么恶心人的嫉妒之旅
- I need your help. - With what, some sick jealousy trip?
-没错  说得好  糖糖  -我证明
- Yes, sing it, Candy! - Testify!
听着  这一切我真的很抱歉
Look, I'm so sorry about everything,
但斯坦现在有麻烦了
but Stan's in trouble.
事后你们怎么处置我都行
You can totally kill me later,
但当务之急  他需要我们
but right now, he needs us.
我会在路上解释的
I'll explain on the way.
求你了  我不知道是不是举头三尺有神明
Please. I don't know if you're really up there or not,
但如果你真的在  请你救救我  保罗・班扬
but if you are, please save me, Paul Bunyan.
（注：美国传说中的巨人樵夫，力大无穷，伐木快如割草。）
派恩斯先生
Mr. Pines!
祈祷成真了
Whoa, did that really work?
快  趁着剩下的毒液还没渗进来
Quick, before the rest of the venom sets in.
不  哪里走
No! Where are you?
缆车  大家快进去
The sky tram, everybody on.
我有个计划
I have a plan.
-哈哈  太好了  -完美
- Ha ha, yeah! - Perfect.
御风疾驰吧  缆车
Ride like the wind, sky tram.
欢迎乘坐“懒车之星”
Welcome to Trambience,
世界上最慢的缆车之行
the world's lowest treetop tram ride.
享受时速零点一迈的风景吧
Enjoy the sights at 0.1 miles per hour.
快动  快动  快动
Move, move, move!
这车厢就不能走快点吗
Can't this thing go any faster?
做不到  这可是“懒车之星”
No, it can't. This is Trambience.
享受到美景了吗  拍张照吧
Enjoying the view? Take a picture.
我们完蛋了
We're doomed!
我们都要死了
We're all gonna die!
大家听好
Listen carefully.
这架缆车设置了一个紧急坠落开关
This sky tram has an emergency drop switch.
我们下方是俄勒冈州最大的保罗・班扬雕塑
Below us is Oregon's largest Paul Bunyan statue.
老伙计喷泉喷发倒数五  四
And Old Reliable goes off in five, four...
糖糖  等等  别拉下控制杆
Candy, wait! Don't pull that lever.
孩子  你疯了吗
Kid, are you crazy?
就是现在
Now!
我唯一的弱点就是巨大的脚
My only weakness, a giant boot.
不过巨大的报纸或者巨大的杯子
A giant newspaper or a giant cup
也很可怕啦
would also have been pretty bad.
感谢您选择乘坐“懒车之星”
Thank you for riding Trambience sky tram.
请把这趟超级超级无聊的旅程推荐给你的朋友
Tell your friends it was a boring, boring ride.
孩子  你刚刚真是太机智了
Kid, that was ingenious!
你怎么知道这样行得通
How'd you know that would work?
是这张没用的旅游小册子上写的
Useless travel pamphlets.
斯坦利
Stanley.
对不起  我不知道自己刚才是怎么了
I'm sorry. I don't know what came over me.
你会救我出来的  对吧
You'll let me out, right?
什么  现在太晚了点儿吧
What? After all that?
有没有搞错  老子看着像得了健忘症吗
Seriously, do I look like an amnesiac?
你真有趣
You're so funny.
你就没想过转行当个喜剧演员吗
Have you ever considered becoming a comedian?
其实  我真想过
You know, I actually have.
现在的喜剧也太小打小闹了
Comedy is too subtle these days.
我的风格可要用上更多的大尺寸道具
My style involves more over-sized props.
-我拉你出来  -不
- Let me get you out-- - No!
对  对
Oh, yeah, right.
这局你赢了  斯坦  但记住我的话
You win this round, Stan, but mark my words.
只要世上还有你这样的男人
As long as there's men like you out there,
还有你们那些愚蠢的俏皮话
with their dumb one-liners,
和搭讪手段  我就不会缺少猎物
and pick-up moves, I'll never run out of prey.
快上车  快上车
Get in the car, get in the car!
好了  孩子  我得承认一件事
All right, kid, I gotta admit something.
我根本不是泡妞专家
I'm no expert on women.
实际上  我离过一次婚
Truth is, I've been divorced once,
被扇耳光的次数多得我自己也数不清
and slapped more times than I can remember.
自信能帮你得到很多东西
Confidence can buy you a lot,
但是到头来
but at the end of the day,
搭讪达人往往会把我们的脑袋咬下来
pick-up artists tend to get our heads bitten off.
面对女人  我很失败
When it comes to women, I'm a failure.
我们都很失败
Hey, we're both failures.
嘿  你的约会小技巧虽然糟糕
You know, even if your dating tips were bad,
但我今天一整天还真没想过温蒂了
I actually haven't thought about Wendy all day.
另外  我的确学到了应该更自信一些
Plus, you did teach me to be more confident.
我想接下来该学的是怎么运用它做好事
I guess I just need to learn to use that power for good.
嘿  我找到一份小册子  你大概还没读过吧
Hey, I found a pamphlet I don't think you've read yet.
废物来道歉
对不起！
超混蛋
我真傻
是真的！
小知识：
对不起，
原谅我好吗？
你最好了！
抱歉
没事的  迪普
It's okay, Dipper.
在阳关大道一路狂奔的确会让人头脑发热
The open road makes people do crazy things.
另外  看了你像个小屁孩一样躲着蜘蛛的样子
Plus, after seeing you flee the spider like a baby,
我好像对你又没兴趣了
I kinda lost interest.
是啊是啊  这是我活该
Yep, yep. I deserve that.
现在进入重力泉镇
我还是感觉有点内疚
I still feel a little bad
损坏了那么多坑游客的景点
about wrecking those tourist traps.
得了  人人都喜欢我的恶作剧
Ah, come on. Everyone loves my pranks.
最棒的是  我从来不需要承担
And the best part is, I never have to face
任何后果  我的天
any consequences... Sweet lord!
不是吧
Ah, come on!
斯坦见鬼去吧
斯坦臭混蛋  甜心奶奶留  派恩斯看好了
你罪有应得  你罪有应得
That's what you get. That's what you get!
我不明白
I don't understand.
我这是招谁惹谁了啊
I completely don't deserve this.
天呐  这个烂摊子得由我们打扫干净吗
Oh, man, are we gonna have to help clean this up?
不  苏斯肯定会料理好这一切的
Nah, I'm sure Soos will take care of it.
话说苏斯哪儿去了
Where is Soos anyway?
好吧  苏斯  记住你奶奶是怎么教你的
Okay, Soos, remember what your grandma taught you.
如果迷路了  你就呆在原地
When you get lost, stay exactly where you are,
不要动
and don't move.
Don't move.
看看  我当稻草人相当不赖呢
You know, I would make a really good scarecrow.